[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the planet that Ripley landed on in Alien 3?", "correct_answer": "Fiorina 161", "incorrect_answers": ["Auriga 5", "Saturn 3", "Nostromo 121"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sore muscles should be excercised...", "correct_answer": "Only youre not sore to the touch", "incorrect_answers": ["Never as it might damage the muscle", "It depends which muscle it is", "Always as it helps heal the soreness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2002, a college research team built a 42-foot bridge across the Raritan River. What were the beams for the bridge made from?", "correct_answer": "Recycled polystyrene cups and milk containers", "incorrect_answers": ["Recycled school erasers", "Recycled tires", "Recycled aluminum cans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1990 movie Ghost starred Demi Moore as Oda Mae Brown.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "George Clooney had a role in the 1978 movie Attack of the Killer Tomatoes.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who tries to warn the driver of the car about the killer in the back seat according to the popular urban legend?", "correct_answer": "A driver of the car behind", "incorrect_answers": ["The signs on the road", "A wolf appearing on the road", "A voice on the radio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A human being can live entirely on a diet consisting only of potatoes and milk.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Two landmark works of horror released in the 19th century were Frankenstein (1818) by Mary Shelley and Dracula (1897) by this Irish author.", "correct_answer": "Bram Stoker", "incorrect_answers": ["W. H. Auden", "Lord Byron", "Robert Louis Stevenson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pathogenic microorganisms which get into the human body are called antigens because they cause the formation of antibodies. The antibodies are produced by what blood cells?", "correct_answer": "Lymphocites", "incorrect_answers": ["Keratinocytes", "Thrombocytes", "Erythrocytes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Beethovens Fifth Symphony is divided into four movements. What is the name of the opening one?", "correct_answer": "Allegro con brio", "incorrect_answers": ["Scherzo: Allegro", "Andante con moto", "Allegro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The phenomenon that leads individual consumers and producers to equilibrium with the market is defined by which term in economics?", "correct_answer": "The invisible hand", "incorrect_answers": ["The free-rider problem", "The price ceiling", "Government regulations"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the sleazy lawyer in the musical and movie Chicago?", "correct_answer": "Billy Flynn", "incorrect_answers": ["Rudy Baylor", "Pete Drucker", "Ted Buckland"]}]